CITY A – HERO ASSOCIATION HQ
Then it is decided that Mumen Rider
will remain the top-ranked class C hero.
Understood. I will let him know.
I simply cannot understand
why he has no desire
to move up to class B...
Our next agenda item is
the 55th Hero Certification Exam.
For this exam,
the total number of candidates is...
11,684, with the exam offered
at six different venues.
That is an increase of more than
22% over the previous exam.
We mustn't be happy
with simple quantity.
Even with more candidates,
if the quality of the heroes
is reduced,
the numbers are meaningless.
Therefore, we ought to be even more
critical during evaluations.
Also, I hear that
a certain person of interest
is taking the exam this time.
Yes, it hasn't been confirmed yet,
but it seems very likely
that he will.
One punch
Three, two, one, kill shot
sanjou, hisshou, shijou saikyou
He joins the fight, he wins, the strongest in history
nan datten da, frustration
Are you talking to him? Frustration ☹
ore wa tomaranai
He's not going to stop
one punch, kanryou, rensenrenshou
One punch, that's it, one fight after another
ore wa katsu, tsune ni katsu, asshou
He wins, he always wins, overwhelmingly
power, get power
Power, get power
girigiri genkai made
On to the very edge
Hero
ore o tataeru koe ya
There are voices praising him
kassai nante hoshiku wa nai sa
but he's not doing this for acclaim
Hero
dakara hitoshirezu aku to tatakau
So he just fight evil without end
Nobody knows who he is
sora ooi oshiyoseru teki
Enemies to fight are numerous as the stars
ore wa se wo muke wa shinai
and he's not gonna turn his back on you
Hero
naraba yuruginaki kakugo shita tame
He's made up his mind and ain't gonna yield
tatakau hero
A fighting hero
kodoku na hero
A lone hero
I
i wanna be a saikyou hero
I wanna be the strongest hero
HERO TEST LOCATION #6
Candidates, please form
two lines for registration.
Next!
Side-to-side jumps for 30 seconds!
Ready...
Go!
Next, the 1500-meter run. Go!
Next, weightlifting!
Next, shot put!
Vertical jumping!
Whack-a-Mole!
Punching machine!
I'm going home...
THE ULTIMATE MASTER
Finally done with all the tests.
Now I just wait for the results.
Oh, you done, too?
Yes.
Hey, is there a point in you
taking fitness tests?
Huh?
I mean, can't you just give them
the data on your specs?
Well, whatever. So how was it?
Both the written and fitness tests
were far too simple.
Right? Is that really all there is
to becoming a hero?
We should get our results soon.
70 points is a passing grade.
The written test was so easy
anyone could get full points on it.
That just leaves the fitness test,
which for us should not have
posed any problems.
— ONE HOUR LATER
I got 100 points.
Seriously?
Yes.
It says I'm certified as
a class S hero.
Class S? What's that?
I am sure these rankings
mean little.
How did you do, Master?
Huh?
Oh! The letter says I'm also...
Class S.
I am not surprised.
On top of that, the font size
is bigger than mine.
I expected nothing less, Master.
By the way, what did they
ask you at the interview?
Interview?
Yes.
Just one final question, Genos.
Does this building
look familiar to you?
We've been secretly investigating
a group of troublemakers
that call themselves
the “House of Evolution.”
Just when we identified
its center of operations,
we found the building had been
mysteriously destroyed.
And with overwhelmingly
intense firepower.
Are you responsible for this?
I am.
Why?
certified S class
I see...
I suppose it must be that
they felt no need to go through
the trouble of interviewing you.
Master?
Yeah, after all...
I'm just a class C hero
with a score of 71 points.
I see.
So I mistakenly thought the top half
of the “C” was part an “S.”
Stop analyzing it!
It must be a mistake.
I will talk to
the person in charge.
No, don't!
You'll just embarrass me!
Mr. Genos, Mr. Saitama,
there will be a seminar for
successful candidates at 4:00 PM.
Please come to lecture hall #3.
All right, come on.
All that really matters
is we passed.
Let's get it over with and go home.
We finally found the cyborg
we've been looking for.
So I've heard.
In consideration of
his past accomplishments,
we made an exception and
certified him as a Class S hero.
I just wanted to make sure
you were notified of this.
Yes, I approve.
Genos, huh?
Lecture Hall 3
First, congratulations on passing.
Now one of you
only made it on a fluke,
so unless you want your luck
to go to waste,
I better see you
giving it your all.
And don't get all puffed up!
From here on, keep your hero status
in mind and act modestly!
After all, your faces will be placed
on the Hero Association website.
Did you hear me?
That goofball head of yours is
gonna be shown to the whole world.
If you don't want to
humiliate yourselves...
Aspire to be a fine hero like me!
Master!
As a class A hero, I have some
influence over the Association.
I'll make sure those who
behave irresponsibly...
lose points and get demoted.
Don't you forget it!
What should I have for dinner?
Apparently, the Hero Association
was formed about three years ago.
So it's only been three years?
It was after the grandchild of
a millionaire called Agoni
was attacked by a monster.
The child was saved by a passerby.
When Agoni heard
what had happened,
he came up with this system
and used his fortune
to establish the Hero Association.
Well, they put on
some pretty boring seminars.
In any case, as new heroes,
we'll be known around the world.
Now we can work with
our heads held high.
Master...
I guess I'm now officially
your disciple.
Please continue to guide me
as my mentor.
Yeah...
All right, Master. Good night.
Yeah, see you.
Crap...
Maybe I shouldn't have been so quick
to say I'd take a disciple.
Especially this guy...
m 50 28 l 522 40 522 210 79 153
OFFICE
Those two newcomers today—
did they really pass the exam?
Their attitudes were awful!
I'm Class A, rank 38 damn it,
and they had no idea who I was.
Plus they don't know the first thing
about how the world works.
Damn amateurs!
They'll be dirt-napping in no time.
No.
Genos got perfect scores on both
the written and physical exams.
He's a phenomenal rookie
who gained a class S ranking
right off the bat.
The other one, Saitama,
had terrible scores on the essay,
but scored a perfect 50
on the physical.
That's how he was able to
pass at all.
But in practically every activity
on the fitness exam,
he broke the Hero Association's test
records by inconceivable margins.
It's as if there's a god
residing in that body.
Snek, you've already been
outranked by Genos.
And Saitama may catch up
with you soon enough.
That jackass?
If I get to the top of class C,
then I'll get promoted to class B...
And class A is above that,
with class S even above that...
I guess Genos is
actually pretty amazing.
I don't know...
...but maybe this isn't
the kind of hero I wanted to be.
The newcomer seminar
isn't over yet!
In this business, there's a thing
called rookie crushing.
A lot of us heroes
hate to be outranked.
So we crush newbies early on...
like this!
Hero Registry?
Yes, I am a class S hero and you
are a class C hero.
We are both ranked last
in our classes.
Right now, we are still listed
as Genos and Saitama,
but as we perform more heroic acts,
we will acquire hero names.
Hero names? What are those?
I believe they are like nicknames
that capture a hero's characteristics.
For example,
I might be the “Blond Cyborg.”
Wait, if that's how it works,
won't I be like the “Caped Baldy?”
Aside from being ranked by ability,
you can also be
ranked by popularity.
There are some heroes
that have fan clubs.
Well, no one cares about that.
Wha—?!
Thank you for agreeing to
my unreasonable request today.
Yeah, well I did promise
to make you my disciple...
Is right here good?
Yes...
So we're just having
a practice bout, right?
Not fighting for real?
Yes, that's what I have in mind.
But I want you to go all out,
so I too will give it my all.
Please grant my request.
That was close...
My clothes could have got
burnt up again.
I need more speed!
He's gone?
Have I been chasing
his afterimage this whole time?
There!
Incinerate!
I got him this time.
Master will have to take me
more seriously now...
Behind—
Okay, I win.
Master...
Yah?
Have you forgotten
the rules of the bout?
Dodge any attack
you are able to dodge.
Take it seriously
and no fooling around.
Do not hold back.
And...
keep fighting until
I am no longer able to fight.
Even Master Saitama himself
cannot explain.
The secret to his power...
This fight may give me
some insight into it.
Show me no mercy.
Those were the rules, Master—
What the—?!
DEATH
I'm starving. Time for lunch.
Let's grab some udon noodles.
Okay...
I am prepared to do anything
in order to become stronger.
But...
I can't picture myself
even approaching Master's power.
Not at all...
He's on a different level.
What's the matter?
You don't like udon?
I see, that's his location?
Thanks, I'll head there now.
No, don't worry.
I'm just going to let him know
what the industry expects of him.
I'm glad you like udon.
Yes, I'm not very picky.
Well, I'm also kinda
low on funds right now...
Hey, how about
another match, Genos?
SUPER-SPICY MEGA-MONSTER UDON CHALLENGE
PRIZE: ¥50,000, FAILURE: ¥10,000
That's insane!
No way!
I give up...
Is that it?
Man, you're awesome!
Welcome?!
You must be Genos.
I'm Amai Mask, class A rank 1.
I'd like to talk to you.
Class A, rank 1?
It's Amai Mask!
He's so gorgeous!
Talk?
He might be a rookie crusher...
Be careful, Genos!
I see. Please wait here, Master.
Very well.
I was just thinking about taking
a walk to digest my food.
I hear you were certified class S
by special exception.
What of it?
I wonder if he's all right...
Done already?
Yes.
You really are class S.
To have the top-ranked class A hero
come to personally crush you...
That's not it.
So he wasn't here to fight?
Then what gives?
In short...
He came to welcome me.
Huh? What's that mean?
Excuse me!
You're friends with
Amai Mask, right?
May I shake your hand?
Thank you very much!
Shake mine too!
Class S and class C heroes
sure get treated differently.
If you think about it, though,
isn't that like fraud money?
WELCOME GIFT
I mean, you're a cyborg, right?
Yes...
Never mind. In any case, now we're
even with a win and a loss apiece.
Starting today
we're professional heroes.
Let's do our best, okay?
Yes.
A professional hero must always be
a beautiful symbol of justice.
That is my philosophy.
It's especially true
if you're a class S hero.
Come on,
there's no need to glare at me.
I came all the way here
just to see you.
How was the Certification Exam?
It was nothing but rubbish.
An exam like that is a waste of time.
If you came to fight, get on with it.
This, too, is a waste of time.
Being hot-blooded is fine,
but if you take it too far...
...you'll get burnt.
I'll forget your criticism
of the Association.
Thank you for your time.
I welcome you to the team.
We expect great things
from you...
Genos.
Master...
I will be back later.
Oh, okay...
I'll see you.
Yes, goodbye.
A waste of time?
Such an interesting fellow...
Hey, come back home soon
On nights when the new moon shivers from my sighs
I close my eyes and think of you
I want to see you... I feel like crying
I feel so romantic
I hope these feelings reach you
I know very well
how hard you work all the time
You're the one I love
You're so strong but I'm still worried
Don't hide your weakness, at least show it to me
I'll find you before any stars
Come straight back home
Hey, come back home soon
Uh...
So when you said,
“I'll be back...”
This is what you meant?
Yes. I went home
to gather my things.
May I live here?
Absolutely not.
I have rent money.
Did you bring a toothbrush?
Yes!
NEXT EPISODE
THE TERRIFYING CITY
I am Snek,
Class A, rank 38!
A lot of guys think
my name is “Snake,”
but it's Snek,
so don't forget it!
Next on One-Punch Man
is episode 6,
The Terrifying City
There's time left?
Well, I'm fully
aware of that.
That's right!
In this industry,
there's such a thing
as killing time with
episode previews!